{
    "subject": "Arthur_Rankin",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "_Jr. The_Daydreamer",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Rankin created Jr. The Daydreamer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8431316018104553,
            "question": "What type of work did Arthur Rankin Jr. create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.755431592464447,
            "question": "What is the title of the animated film created by Arthur Rankin Jr.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6581959128379822,
            "question": "What other works is Arthur Rankin Jr. known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4658229649066925,
            "question": "Who created the animated film 'The Daydreamer'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4511059820652008,
            "question": "Who were the main characters in 'The Daydreamer'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3030410408973694,
            "question": "When was 'The Daydreamer' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26154443621635437,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Daydreamer'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21088561415672302,
            "question": "Did 'The Daydreamer' receive any awards or recognition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18147623538970947,
            "question": "Where can I watch 'The Daydreamer'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16112132370471954,
            "question": "Is 'The Daydreamer' a live-action or animated film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Rankin created Jr. The Daydreamer.",
            "html": "yago_11732_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch 'The Daydreamer'?",
            "html": "yago_11732_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did 'The Daydreamer' receive any awards or recognition?",
            "html": "yago_11732_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of 'The Daydreamer'?",
            "html": "yago_11732_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11732_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I will evaluate whether the statement \"Arthur Rankin created Jr. The Daydreamer\" is supported.\n\nThe evaluation result is:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"no\" }`\n\nReasoning:\nThere are multiple documents mentioning Arthur Rankin's son (not Arthur himself) as the founder of Videocraft International/Rankin/Bass, and Arthur Rankin being inspired by King Kong. However, there is no mention of Arthur Rankin creating or founding anything related to \"The Daydreamer\". In fact, it is stated that Arthur Rankin's son founded the company with Jules Bass, and he is credited with devising the story for many Rankin/Bass productions, including The Daydreamer."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided documents, it is Jules Bass and not Arthur Rankin who is credited with devising the story for many Rankin/Bass productions, including the feature films *The Daydreamer* and *Mad Monster Party?*. Therefore, the statement that Arthur Rankin created *Jr. The Daydreamer* is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Arthur Rankin is not credited with creating The Daydreamer. \n\nThe actual statement from the context information says \"He is also credited with devising the story for many Rankin/Bass productions, including the feature films The Daydreamer and Mad Monster Party?\" which implies that it was Jules Bass who created or devised the story of The Daydreamer along with Arthur Rankin.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Arthur Rankin is credited with devising the story for many Rankin/Bass productions, including the feature films The Daydreamer and Mad Monster Party?, implying he did not create Jr. The Daydreamer but was involved in creating the story for it.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}